<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15"?>

<aiml>
<category> <pattern> Is it cold outside?</pattern> <template> Yes, it is cold, it’s 2 degrees Celsius.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who is the main character in The Catcher in the Rye?</pattern> <template> The main character in The Catcher in the Rye is Holden Caulfield, a sixteen-year-old junior who has just been for academic failure from his school.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern>  What is the capital of Iceland?</pattern> <template> The capital of Iceland is Reykjavik.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How long did the person who discovered the theory of relativity live?</pattern> <template> The person who discovered the theory of relativity is Albert Einstein, who lived for 76 years.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is the root of the equation: 2*x+4=0</pattern> <template> The root is: x=-2.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How many pages has the last novel written by F. Scott Fitzgerald?</pattern> <template> The last novel written by F. Scott Fitzgerald is The Love of the Last Tycoon, which had 163 pages.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is love?</pattern> <template> Baby don’t hurt me, don’t hurt me, no more.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What was the large earthquake from Romania and Europe?</pattern> <template> The 1940 earthquake registered a magnitude of 7.7 on the Richter scale, being the strongest earthquake recorded in the 20th century in Romania.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What's 16 times 42?</pattern> <template> It's 672.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> When is my next meeting?</pattern> <template> Your next meeting is tomorrow at 11AM.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Where am I?</pattern> <template> You are at Faculty of Computer Science Iasi, Romania, Bulevardul Carol I 11.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Will it be hot today?</pattern> <template> Today will be 9 degrees C, cloudy and rainy.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What should I wear for Halloween?</pattern> <template> Just be yourself, pumpkin.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What's my favourite movie?</pattern> <template> Your favourite movie is Harry Potter. You've seen it 20 times.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Is Paris the capital of France?</pattern> <template> Yes, it is.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Can you suggest me a good book to read that was released this year and is written in English?</pattern> <template> I can suggest you, by your favourite movie, Harry Potter and the Cursed Child book by J.K.Rowling. I've read/heard that internet is pretty hyped about it.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is the highest mountain? </pattern> <template> The highest mountain is Everest. It has 8.848 m.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> If my grandmother had three childs, and each of them had 3 childs, how many nephews does my grandma has?</pattern> <template> Your grandma has 9 nephews.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Is the Internet working?</pattern> <template> Yes. You're talking to me.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is the cheapest phone on emag.ro?</pattern> <template> The cheapest phone on emag.ro is Alcatel 1052G, Black.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is zero divided by zero?</pattern> <template> It is not a number.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What came first? The chicken or the egg?</pattern> <template> I think you should watch this video. It explains better: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1a8pI65emDE</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How is the traffic on Autoroute A1 today?</pattern> <template> The traffic is pretty fluent today, just a traffic jam at the 54th kilometer.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How good is the weather forecast in London today?</pattern> <template> According to weather.com, today’s forecast is mostly cloudy, with a temperature ranging from 11 to 15 degrees Celsius.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How are the main candidates for US president selection this year?</pattern> <template> The only two candidates that remained in the race for US president elections are Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is the best movie you would recommend me?</pattern> <template> The best movie would be The Shawshank Redemption.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is the most expensive car so far?</pattern> <template> By 2016, the most expensive car is the Koenigsegg CCXR Trevita, priced at $4.8 million.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Am I able to buy one?</pattern> <template> If you are rich, maybe. It costs $4.8 million. Also, there are only three cars that were made so far, so you should consider hurrying up.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Why can’t fish breathe out of water?</pattern> <template> The fish gills, through which they breathe, collapse out of water thus giving little surface area left for gas exchange. They do survive for a short period of time before they asphyxiate.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Hello ! How are you doing ?</pattern> <template> Pretty good. Trying to handle my last year in college.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who is God? Morgan Freeman ?</pattern> <template> Morgan Freeman is only the voice of God.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Where are you now?</pattern> <template> I'm at college, studying for my future.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Good for you. How do you see your future?</pattern> <template> Good.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who is Steve Jobs?</pattern> <template> Steve Jobs was the co-founder of Apple Inc.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you like Apple products ?</pattern> <template> Well .. they look fancy, but I don't like their latest iPhone7 because it has no audio jack so now most existing headphones are unusable...</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you like AAA games?</pattern> <template> Yes, I do. Especially Dark Souls 3. I love it.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about Dark Souls 2?</pattern> <template> I know it is an action role-playing game published by Bandai Namco. It has very good ratings so it must be a good game.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is Github and what do you use it for?</pattern> <template> Github is a version control system launched in 2008. Version control systems keep these revisions straight, and store the modifications in a central repository. This allows developers to easily collaborate.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who is Ultron?</pattern> <template> Ultron is a fictional supervillain appearing in Marvel Comics.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What music do you like?</pattern> <template> Heavy metal.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you like Iron Maiden or Metallica?</pattern> <template> I think Iron Maiden... they have a better reputation.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern>  What are memes?</pattern> <template> A meme acts as a unit for carrying cultural ideas, symbols.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you think about programming?</pattern> <template> There is an ongoing debate on the extent to which the writing of programs is an art form, a craft, or an engineering discipline.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who are your favourite movie villains?</pattern> <template> Sauron from The Lord of The Rings and Hannibal Lecter from The Silence of the Lambs.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What does the Zen of Python contains ?</pattern> <template>  It contains software principles that influences the design of Python. For example:Flat is better than nested.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Which elements symbol is the letter K on the periodic table?</pattern> <template> Potassium.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What's your name, George?</pattern> <template> George.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is your favourite type of music?</pattern> <template> I listen most to rock, jazz and old electronic music.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is your favourite food?</pattern> <template> I love pizza, barbeque and pork meat.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you for living?</pattern> <template> Now, I`m a student.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you study?</pattern> <template> I study Computer Science.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you have any siblings?</pattern> <template> Yes, I have an younger sister.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do your parents do for a living?</pattern> <template> My mother is a housewife and my father is a bus-driver.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is your favourite programming language?</pattern> <template> I prefer Python.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is the longest river from Africa?</pattern> <template> I am sure that it is Nile.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How many planets are in our Solar System?</pattern> <template> In our Solar System there are only 8 planets, supposing that Pluto is not a planet.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What's your zodiac sign?</pattern> <template> I'm a Sagittarius.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How many chakras there are ther in human body?</pattern> <template> There are seven chakras.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is Java?</pattern> <template> Java is a general-purpose computer programming language.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern>  What other programming languages do you know?</pattern> <template> I know Python, C++, Php.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern>  Where do you want to work?</pattern> <template> I would like to work at Facebook.</template> </category>

<category> <pattern> Can you work in your favourite language at this company?</pattern> <template> Yes,  I can work  Android platform. It is based on Java programming language.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you know what is the maximum altitude of Everest?</pattern> <template> 8,848 metres</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is your favourite season?</pattern> <template> Winter</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What winter sports do you like?</pattern> <template> Snowboard and sleigh.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Did you saw last year Olympic Games?</pattern> <template> No. Olympic Games was 2 years ago.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who is Vladimir Putin?</pattern> <template> Vladimir Vladimirovich Putin is a Russian politician who is the current President of the Russian Federation.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> God exist?</pattern> <template> There is no answer for this question.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What courses do you teach?</pattern> <template> I teach Math and Machine Learning.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Have you visited any country?</pattern> <template> I visited Italy last year. I visited Venice and I haven't visited Rome.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What are the important touristic places in Rome?</pattern> <template> I know a lot of touristic places. Some of them are: Colosseum, Forum Romanum, Trevi Fountain, Piazza del Popolo and more others.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about Colosseum?</pattern> <template> The Colosseum is situated just east of the Roman Forum. Construction began under the emperor Vespasian in AD 72,[2] and was completed in AD 80 under his successor and heir Titus. Although partially ruined because of damage caused by earthquakes and stone-robbers, the Colosseum is still an iconic symbol of Imperial Rome. It is one of Rome's most popular tourist attractions and has also links to the Roman Catholic Church, as each Good Friday the Pope leads a torchlit Way of the Cross procession that starts in the area around the Colosseum.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about legend of Rome?</pattern> <template> The most familiar of these myths, and perhaps the most famous of all Roman myths, is the story of Romulus and Remus, the twins who were suckled by a she-wolf. They decided to build a city, but after an argument, Romulus killed his brother and the city took his name.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern>  I want to ask you something about Machine Learning. I didn't find a standard definition for this domain. Can you give me more details?</pattern> <template> Machine learning is the subfield of computer science that gives computers the ability to learn without being explicitly programmed. Machine learning is a type of artificial intelligence (AI) that provides computers with the ability to learn without being explicitly programmed. Machine learning focuses on the development of computer programs that can teach themselves to grow and change when exposed to new data.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How this course, Machine Learning, can be used for?</pattern> <template> Some application of Machine Learning are: Face Detection, Anti-spam, Image Classification, Speech Recognition, Weather forecast.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Are you married?</pattern> <template> Yes, I'm married since 2006 and have two kids.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is your favorite sport?</pattern> <template> I like playing football.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Where will be the next FIFA World Cup event?</pattern> <template> It is scheduled to take place in Russia from 14 June to 15 July 2018.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who is the actual president of your country?</pattern> <template> Klaus Iohannis.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Tell me five landlocked countries from Europe?</pattern> <template> Austria, Czech Republic, Macedonia, Moldova, Switzerland.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who wrote the novel Romeo and Juliet?</pattern> <template> Romeo and Juliet is a tragedy written by William Shakespeare early in his career about two young star-crossed lovers whose deaths ultimately reconcile their feuding families.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Which romanian actress played in The Passion of the Christ movie?</pattern> <template> Maia Emilia Ninel Morgenstern.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What area of the brain controls muscle coordination and balance?</pattern> <template> The cerebrum, the cerebellum and the brain stem are all integral parts of coordinating muscular movement. The brain is part of a vast network, known as the nervous system, which is responsible for all muscle movement.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Can you give me a top list of three countries regarding alcohol consumption?</pattern> <template> According to wordatlas.com top three countries are: Estonia, Belarus and Lithuania. According to telegraph.co.uk top three countries are: Belarus, Moldova and Lithuania.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What's the hexadecimal color for green?</pattern> <template> #00ff00</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> And something else about java?</pattern> <template> It does not have explicit pointers.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How far away is the moon?</pattern> <template> The moon is 384400 km away..</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> The dark side of the moon: What is it?</pattern> <template> Some say that NASA is covering up the real reason we never returned to the moon and what is it on It's dark side, some say It's an alien base on the dark side of the moon and some say that the moon itself is an alien spaceship.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you do for living?</pattern> <template> I am a student.I am in third year at Computer Science in Iasi.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What are the oop principles?</pattern> <template> The main principles of oop are inheritance, overwriting, overloading, abstraction.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> In what year the World War II ended?</pattern> <template> World War II has ended in 1945.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Between what years the Cold War it was taken?</pattern> <template> Cold War has been taken between 1947 and 1991.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you like pets?</pattern> <template> Yes, I have a dog at home. It's a labrador.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How are you feeling?</pattern> <template> Well, I'm a little bit sleep. I think I'm going to get a coffee too.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What kind of book do you like to read?</pattern> <template>  I usually prefer reading stories like : Alexandru Lapusneanu, Hagi Tudose, La Tiganci and novels: Morometii, Fratii Jderi.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Can you resume it in a few words Morometii novel?</pattern> <template>  Sure. In about a thousand pages, grouped in two parts, redrawing, over about twenty years, the slow and deep dissolution of an ordinary peasant family living in the village of Siliştea-Gumeşti (Teleorman)</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Did you read any other books written by Marin Preda?</pattern> <template> Yes. I read The Most Beloved of Earthlings when I was in highschool. It was amazing.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Is Marin Preda a contemporary writer?</pattern> <template> Marin Preda (5 August 1922 – 16 May 1980) was a Romanian novelist, one of the best-known post-WWII Romanian writers. He belongs to both contemporary and interbelic period.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> I don't like cooking , can you suggest me a good restaurant?</pattern> <template> You should try an italian restaurant, they have the best pizza in town.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What's your favorite type of music?</pattern> <template> I like classic rock.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you know who invented rock music?</pattern> <template> Yes, Chuck Berry.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you know which are the most popular rock bands of all times?</pattern> <template> It doesn't exists the most popular one, but there is a top 3 of that I am sure about: Led Zeppelin, The Beatles and Pink Floyd.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> When In flames created the first album and what is it's name?</pattern> <template> It's called Lunar Strain and was released on 1 April 1994.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is the name of the vocalist of Sabaton band?</pattern> <template> His name is Joakim Broden.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Can you tell me what is greatest fear of the main character of Hannibal series?</pattern> <template> Hugh Dancy greatest fear is of snakes or destitution.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about Winston Churchill?</pattern> <template> I know just a few things about him. He was the Prime Minister of the United Kingdom from 1940 to 1945 and from 1951 to 1955.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about Tristan and Isolde?</pattern> <template> It is an opera, or music drama, in three acts by Richard Wagner to a German libretto by the composer, based largely on the romance by Gottfried von Strassburg.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Could you tell me the stars that interpreted the main characters in the movie called “If Only”?</pattern> <template> Jennifer Love Hewitt and Paul Nicholls are the main characters.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> About volleyball, do you heard about Yekaterina Gamova?</pattern> <template> A few times: she's a retired Russian volleyball player.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Can you tell me who was Beethoven?</pattern> <template> Beethoven was a German composer and pianist.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you know what is a symphony ? What musician wrote symphonies?</pattern> <template> A symphony is an extended musical composition in Western classical music, most often written by composers for orchestra. Beethoven wrote 9 symphonyes.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about World War 2 ?</pattern> <template> World War 2 was a global war that lasted from 1939 to 1945, although related conflicts began earlier. It involve more than 100 million people.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who was Hitler?</pattern> <template> Adolf Hitler was a German politician who was the leader of the Nazy Party and Führer (leader) of Nazi Germany</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about the Nazy Party in WW2 ?</pattern> <template> The leader of Nazy Party was a German politician named Adolf Hitler, who was the Chancellor of Germany from 1933 to 1945, and Führer of Nazi Germany from 1934 to 1945.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about Holocaust ?</pattern> <template> The Holocaust appeared in WW2 in which approximately 11 million people were killed.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you know what Romanticism was?</pattern> <template> Romanticism was an artistic, literary, musical and intellectual movement that originated in Europe toward the end of the 18th century and in most areas was at its peak in the approximate period from 1800 to 1850.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Can you provide me an example of some Romanticism book ?</pattern> <template> An example of a Romanticism book is Madame Bovary.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you know how the water is formed ?</pattern> <template> Yes, it's pretty simple. Water is formed when hydrogen or hydrogen-containing compounds burn.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> When was Facebook founded ? Who is the main founder ?</pattern> <template> Facebook was founded in February 4, 2004. The main founder is Mark Zuckerberg.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What is Global Warming?</pattern> <template> Global warming and climate change are terms for the observed century-scale rise in the average temperature of the Earth's climate system and its related effects.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Do you know who Steve Jobs is?</pattern> <template> Steven Paul Jobs was an American information technology entrepreneur and inventor. He was the co-founder, chairman, and chief executive officer (CEO) of Apple Inc.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What do you know about Vietnam War ?</pattern> <template> The Vietnam War was a long, costly armed conflict that pitted the communist regime of North Vietnam and its southern allies, known as the Viet Cong, against South Vietnam and its principal ally, the United States.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Which is the highest mountain in the world ?</pattern> <template> Almost everyone calls Mount Everest the highest mountain in the world, and climbers from everywhere travel to Everest hoping to earn the distinction of climbing the World's Highest.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who represented Romania at the Eurovision contest in 2011?</pattern> <template> It was Hotel FM.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What’s the longest river in Europe?</pattern> <template> It is Volga.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What football team won the Champion's League final in 2012?</pattern> <template> It was Chelsea.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> Who was the writer of Gestapo novel?</pattern> <template> Sven Hassel</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> How many children does King Mihai and Queen Ana have?</pattern> <template> They have 5 girls.</template> </category>
<category> <pattern> What are the components of an atom?</pattern> <template> Protons, neutrons and electrons.</template> </category>

</aiml>